CONTACT

Location: Prague, Czech Republic Telephone: +420 773 879 145 Email: holonalukas@protonmail.com

Website: www.kncpt.art

PERSONAL PROFILE

99 My name is Lukas Holona, 26 years old. I studied at Gymnasium Petra Bezruce. After high school I studied Architecture on Technical University of Ostrava. After four semesters I left and moved to England, where I was working for two years and improved my english language. Currently I'm working in iStep, in Prague as a Visual Designer and learning each day.

LUKAS HOLONA

UX DESIGNER | SWIFT & FRONT END ENTHUSIAST | D.THINKER

EDUCATION

Architecture

Technical University, Ostrava 2012 - 2014

User Experience Fundamentals

IDF - e-learning, Denmark 2017 - Present

SKILLS

// PROFESSIONAL

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Sketch Anima, Craft,... Axure RP HTML, CSS Swift

// ABSTRACT

Critical and design thinking Prototyping Marketing & Analytics Team player

EXPERTISE

- User Experience Design
- Graphic Design
- Customer Experience

CERTIFICATIONS

Interaction Design Foundation
Design Thinking
Practical Guide to Usability
User Research methods
Gestalt Psychology
Emotional design
User Intefrace fundamentals

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Visual Designer

iStep CE - TravelPortal.cz | Prague

2016 - Present

I'm responsible for design system of the company. From letterheads to banner campaigns. I have experience with print campaigns (subway trains), offline (television) as well as with online campaigns (seznam, crymtan, google, adssets). I'm also responsible for dynamic banners using XML feeds to present TravelPortal.cz hotels and destinations, which are unique and innovative in travel industry.

From routine Photoshop and Illustrator work, I use XD and Sketch to design new fuctionality for our web platform TravelPortal.cz. I have been designing mobile version for TravelPortal.cz as well as Affiliate website (which is not live).

I also have good understanding of the current businness model as well. I'm responsible for visual design of TravelPortal.cz newsletters as well as I was in charge of sending weekly emails for two companies. We are using Mailchimp (earlier APSIS) platform and it's automatizations, planning and A/B testing. I also made all kinds of interactive social media posts. (360 images, videos with animations and much more).

I'm able to read data from Google analytics and Hotjar and implement my findings into working design. We made great progress with Hotjar platform as it convinced our stakeholders to explore different options and increase sales potential.

I have partial experience with conducting design sprint and full experience with detection user experience pain points.

In 2019 I was setting up user research brief with marketing and analytical agency for improving our current website usability and conversion rate. This research showed us some major issues which I will implement in new website design I'm currently working on.

I have understanding for development hand-off, because of my knowledge how html, css, js and swift works. I wrote my portfolio myself and I'm intensively learning how to build apps in swift language. (I also already wrote some simple ones). As you can see I'm very versatile when it comes to my skills. Each section I have mentioned is important to me because it can offer different perspective on a problem and might bring better solution.

Graphic Designer & Filmmaking

24production | Prague

2013 - 2017

This was my first work in the digital design field. We have been doing small design works as well as video presendations of products. Our clients - small bussinesses trying to be seen more.

GPA Golf tour - 12 Video Reporting series from golf season. FotbalGolf Praha, Sabroso Restaurant, SPEI Autoservice, Arai Helmets and many more.

CERTIFICATIONS

Udemy Web Developer Course iOS 12 & Swift

HOBBIES

Reading Design meetups Psychology Philosophy Occasional drawing Running

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE (CONTINUE)

I was also designing websites, not only for ourselves, but for BulletIN Advokacie, or MakuFashion.

Admin Clerk & Stock Investigation

2015 - 2016

Boots UK | Burton-upon-Trent

I was one of the leading members of our investigation team in Boots Warehouse. My job was to look for faulty items in the system and make sure it's being delivered to the correct place and correct time.

Although this teached me alot, I didn't really prefer this position and it was purely for language experience purpouses.

Admin Clerk

2014 - 2015

Clipper - SuperDry | Burton-upon-Trent

Making hourly reports what has been picked. Creating picking list for more than 20 picking members. Colaborating with supervisors and other departments.